High Heat is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Zach Golden.
When the local mafia shows up to burn down her restaurant, Ana, a chef with a meticulous past,
defends her turf and proves her knife skills both in and out of the kitchen.
Ana, played by Olga Kurylenko.
Ray, played by Don Johnson.
Tom, played by Chris Diamantopoulos.
Mimi, played by Kaitlin Doubleday.
Dom, played by Page Falkinburg Jr..
Sebastian, played by Dylan Flashner.
High Heat is a 2022 action film directed by Zach Golden
with a screenplay written by James Pedersen.
The film stars Olga Kurylenko and Don Johnson.
The film was released on December 16, 2022, both in
theaters and on streaming platforms.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.